[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "The big question everyone is asking, why did you waive Jerry Sandusky's rights to have this hearing today?", "question_tokens": ["The", "big", "question", "everyone", "is", "asking", ",", "why", "did", "you", "waive", "Jerry", "Sandusky", "'s", "rights", "to", "have", "this", "hearing", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Unprecedented in large cases, normal in almost everyday cases, I have to point that out.", "answer_tokens": ["Unprecedented", "in", "large", "cases", ",", "normal", "in", "almost", "everyday", "cases", ",", "I", "have", "to", "point", "that", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "You've taken a big gamble, haven't you, in removing your client's right to have all that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "taken", "a", "big", "gamble", ",", "have", "n't", "you", ",", "in", "removing", "your", "client", "'s", "right", "to", "have", "all", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "We have.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Are you a pedophile?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "pedophile", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Am I sexually attracted to underage boys?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "sexually", "attracted", "to", "underage", "boys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "I mean, do you see to, again, an impartial observer just how awful that sounded?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "see", "to", ",", "again", ",", "an", "impartial", "observer", "just", "how", "awful", "that", "sounded", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Taken in a vacuum, I can't disagree with you.", "answer_tokens": ["Taken", "in", "a", "vacuum", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "disagree", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "ORGAN: But tell me this, when you hear a man of Jerry Sandusky's age talking about having horseplay with naked 10, 11, 12- year-old boys in showers, don't you think to yourself, this is very, very strange behavior for a man of that age?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "But", "tell", "me", "this", ",", "when", "you", "hear", "a", "man", "of", "Jerry", "Sandusky", "'s", "age", "talking", "about", "having", "horseplay", "with", "naked", "10", ",", "11", ",", "12-", "year-old", "boys", "in", "showers", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "think", "to", "yourself", ",", "this", "is", "very", ",", "very", "strange", "behavior", "for", "a", "man", "of", "that", "age", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I do think it's strange behavior for a man of that age.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "think", "it", "'s", "strange", "behavior", "for", "a", "man", "of", "that", "age", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "If you were prosecuting this, given the sheer wealth of allegations and the volume of people making them, would you feel pretty confident of at least some form of conviction here?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "prosecuting", "this", ",", "given", "the", "sheer", "wealth", "of", "allegations", "and", "the", "volume", "of", "people", "making", "them", ",", "would", "you", "feel", "pretty", "confident", "of", "at", "least", "some", "form", "of", "conviction", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Let me ask you first, Bobby, why have you done this?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "first", ",", "Bobby", ",", "why", "have", "you", "done", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I believe I'm coming forth to help children, to give them the courage to talk.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "I", "'m", "coming", "forth", "to", "help", "children", ",", "to", "give", "them", "the", "courage", "to", "talk", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bobby"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "Was the real problem here, as it seems to have been at Penn State as well that these kind of coaches at college level in America are put on to this kind of god- like plinth, you know, they're almost untouchable, and they start to believe they're untouchable?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "the", "real", "problem", "here", ",", "as", "it", "seems", "to", "have", "been", "at", "Penn", "State", "as", "well", "that", "these", "kind", "of", "coaches", "at", "college", "level", "in", "America", "are", "put", "on", "to", "this", "kind", "of", "god-", "like", "plinth", ",", "you", "know", ",", "they", "'re", "almost", "untouchable", ",", "and", "they", "start", "to", "believe", "they", "'re", "untouchable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "That is true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Penn State"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Boeheim"]}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Why go after him?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "go", "after", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Well, Piers, because Coach Boeheim was the coach of -- and is the coach of the Syracuse men's basketball team.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "because", "Coach", "Boeheim", "was", "the", "coach", "of", "--", "and", "is", "the", "coach", "of", "the", "Syracuse", "men", "'s", "basketball", "team", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Does that apology make any difference to you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "apology", "make", "any", "difference", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Too little, too late, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Too", "little", ",", "too", "late", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike", "Bobby", "Mr. Fine"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "The statute of limitations does apply in New York to bar Mike and Bobby from any criminal case prosecution of Mr. Fine.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "statute", "of", "limitations", "does", "apply", "in", "New", "York", "to", "bar", "Mike", "and", "Bobby", "from", "any", "criminal", "case", "prosecution", "of", "Mr.", "Fine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Do you think that Jim Boeheim, given what he's said about you guys -- do you think he should be fired, given he's now tried to retract his comments?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "Jim", "Boeheim", ",", "given", "what", "he", "'s", "said", "about", "you", "guys", "--", "do", "you", "think", "he", "should", "be", "fired", ",", "given", "he", "'s", "now", "tried", "to", "retract", "his", "comments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "That's not for me to say.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "for", "me", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim Boeheim"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Do you think this goes back to that sense of they're just to powerful to touch these guys?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "this", "goes", "back", "to", "that", "sense", "of", "they", "'re", "just", "to", "powerful", "to", "touch", "these", "guys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I think they do feel like that, in a sense.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "they", "do", "feel", "like", "that", ",", "in", "a", "sense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What do you make of the way this race is now unraveling as we head towards Iowa?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "way", "this", "race", "is", "now", "unraveling", "as", "we", "head", "towards", "Iowa", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "I appreciate the fact that you indicated to your audience that I'm not terribly objective.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "appreciate", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "indicated", "to", "your", "audience", "that", "I", "'m", "not", "terribly", "objective", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iowa"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jon Huntsman", "Jon Huntsman"]}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Who would you rather President Obama face, when push comes to shove?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "you", "rather", "President", "Obama", "face", ",", "when", "push", "comes", "to", "shove", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "First of all, I like Jon Huntsman, too, which probably isn't going to do Jon Huntsman any good in the Republican party.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "like", "Jon", "Huntsman", ",", "too", ",", "which", "probably", "is", "n't", "going", "to", "do", "Jon", "Huntsman", "any", "good", "in", "the", "Republican", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "How does he avoid the banana skin?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "he", "avoid", "the", "banana", "skin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "First of all, I wouldn't say I self-imploded.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "say", "I", "self-imploded", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "What did you make of that comment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "comment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Well, it's very colorful, obviously.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "colorful", ",", "obviously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Should America just allow this drone, with all of the technology, to be sitting there in Iranian hands?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "America", "just", "allow", "this", "drone", ",", "with", "all", "of", "the", "technology", ",", "to", "be", "sitting", "there", "in", "Iranian", "hands", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Look, that's what's got us into Iraq, go in and blow everything apart.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "'s", "got", "us", "into", "Iraq", ",", "go", "in", "and", "blow", "everything", "apart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2003", "2004"], "ORGANIZATION": ["United States Army"], "LOCATION": ["Camp Ashram", "Baghdad"]}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "What can you tell me about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "can", "you", "tell", "me", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Well, there are 3,400 men and women at Camp Ashram, which is about 60 miles northeast of Baghdad, surrendered their means of self-protection to the United States Army in 2003 and 2004.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "3,400", "men", "and", "women", "at", "Camp", "Ashram", ",", "which", "is", "about", "60", "miles", "northeast", "of", "Baghdad", ",", "surrendered", "their", "means", "of", "self-protection", "to", "the", "United", "States", "Army", "in", "2003", "and", "2004", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.N."]}, "docId": "111213pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "In simple terms, how should the president deal with Iran?", "question_tokens": ["In", "simple", "terms", ",", "how", "should", "the", "president", "deal", "with", "Iran", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Well, I mean, every time we go to the U.N. to try to get a sanction, we -- they end up building a couple more centrifuges.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "every", "time", "we", "go", "to", "the", "U.N.", "to", "try", "to", "get", "a", "sanction", ",", "we", "--", "they", "end", "up", "building", "a", "couple", "more", "centrifuges", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}]